William F. Kimball legislative papers, 1941-1954
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
William F. Kimball legislative papers, 1941-1954
AZ 293
Kimball, William F., 1909-1962
This collection includes hearings, minutes, bills, correspondence, clippings, and related reference material from the Senate Appropriations Committee, the Senate Judiciary Committee and other committees of which Kimball was a member.
1.7 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Biographical Note
William F. Kimball was a Arizona State Senator from Pima County; from the15th to the 21st Legislative Session.
Organization
This collection is organized into two series:
Series I: Legislative Sessions, 1941-1954
Series II: Miscellaneous Material
Scope and Content Note
This collection includes hearings, minutes, bills, correspondence, clippings, and related reference material from the Senate Appropriations Committee, the Senate Judiciary Committee and other committees of which Kimball was a member.
Access Terms
Arizona. -- Legislature. -- Senate.
Arizona. Legislature -- Appropriations and expenditures
Arizona -- Politics and government
Bills (legislative)
Container List
- Series I: Legislative Sessions, 1941-1954
  - 15th Legislature: Miscellaneous bills, memorials, etc. 1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 15th Legislature: Senate Appropriations Committee, Senate Bill 4: State Hospital. 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 16th Legislature: Governor's Budget Message. January 18, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 16th Legislature: General Appropriations Bill. 1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 16th Legislature: Senate Appropriations Committee Hearings, A-Z. 1943 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  - 16th Legislature: Senate Judiciary Committee Minutes. 1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 16th Legislature: Senate Judiciary Committee Senate Bill 15, Mutual Benefit Corporations. 1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 16th Legislature: Senate Judiciary Committee Senate Bill 33, Arizona Teachers Retirement System. 1943 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 16th Legislature: Senate Judiciary Committee Senate Bill 50, Public Highway Transportation. 1943 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 16th Legislature: Senate Judiciary Committee Senate Bill 52, Planning and Zoning. 1943 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 16th Legislature: Senate Committee on State Institutions. 1943 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 16th Legislature: Miscellaneous Senate and House Bills. 1943 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 17th Legislature: Senate Appropriations Committee Hearings, A-Z. 1945 (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
  - 17th Legislature: Senate Bills 1-59. 1945 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
  - 17th Legislature: Senate Bills 61-116, Resolutions, etc. 1945 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 17th Legislature: Senate Judiciary Committee. 1945 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 17th Legislature: Senate Committee of the Whole. 1945 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 17th Legislature: House Bills. 1945 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 17th Legislature: Legislative Digest, issued by the Arizona Tax Research Association. January 1945-March 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 18th Legislature: Budget requests, miscellaneous material. 1947 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 19th Legislature: Senate Appropriations Committee Hearings, A-Z. 1949 (Box 3, Folder 6-8)
  - 19th Legislature: Miscellaneous material. 1949 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 20th Legislature: Special Legislative Committee on State Operations. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 20th Legislature: House Bills proposed. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 20th Legislature: Miscellaneous material. 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 21st Legislature: Senate Appropriations Committee. 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 21st Legislature: Proposals and Studies on Taxation. 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 21st Legislature: Miscellaneous House Bills. 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Series II: Miscellaneous Material
  - William F. Kimball: Legislative Record and Miscellaneous Personal Material. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Governor Howard Pyle: Miscellaneous speeches. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "Constitutional Law" notes. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous items. (Box 4, Folder 10)